hanzo at your service
why did you abandon the assassins art
i never was an assassin i killed only
because it was necessary
hanzo you should consider joining us
i think we'd see eye to eye i would have
little to gain from such an arrangement
no i will find my own path
you disappoint me hanzo with talon
you could truly fulfill your destiny
find another errand boy akande
what's wrong hanzo don't you recognize
me
you may call yourself my brother but you
are not the genji are you
so this is what has become of you
a pity i will not be judged by you
it is not too late to change our course
brother you are mistaken brother
i am beyond redemption together
we could have built an empire that was
your dream
not mine we could have built an
empire together so was your dream
not mine you
will never amount to anything we shall
see
brother what would our father think of
what we've become brother
it's hard to say who he'd been more
disappointed by
think you can do better than me i am
certain of it any chocolates today
brother
those were your amusements not mine
i do not fear death no
you find living the challenge
where did you hide your treasure you
could hardly have it on your person
treasure sure i don't know anything
you're talking about
you know that sake is not half bad but i
prefer a little
bite in my liquor how predictable such
an
unsophisticated taste
order and discipline that is the only
way to live
i sense a kindred spirit
i would wager on my bow against your
rifle
any day that would be the last mistake
you ever made
i would take my bow against your rifle
any day
that would be the last mistake you ever
made
talon could restore your family's empire
but at what
cost
i sense within you the same rage that
once consumed your brother
we are nothing alike
just as when we were boys
were never my equal how
elegant
it's not my fault if people want to pick
me all the time
they simply recognize greatness when
they see it